<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CrazyKids&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CrazyKids&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 22:41:35 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Convert Datetime to Timestamp - Free Tool | DevUtils</title>
      <link>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/timestamps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 22:41:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/timestamps/</guid>
      <description>Free online timestamp converter! Quickly convert datetime to Unix timestamp or timestamp to datetime, supports multiple formats, try now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memora: Read It Later App for iOS &amp; macOS with Offline Reading</title>
      <link>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/memora/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 23:06:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/memora/</guid>
      <description>Memora is a secure read it later app for iOS and macOS. Save web pages offline, sync via iCloud, and enjoy distraction-free reading. Organize with tags and search easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>xvm: Version Manager on windows for Node.js, Go, Python</title>
      <link>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/xvm-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 23:21:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/xvm-windows/</guid>
      <description>xvm is an extendable version manager on windows for Node.js, Go, and Python. Learn to manage multiple language versions with this open-source tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>xvm: Version Manager for Node.js, Go, Python</title>
      <link>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/xvm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/xvm/</guid>
      <description>xvm is an extendable version manager for Node.js, Go, and Python. Learn to manage multiple language versions with this open-source tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yellow Screen</title>
      <link>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/yellow-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:34:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/yellow-screen/</guid>
      <description>Step into Blackscreen.space and experience the ultimate allure of yellow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Screen</title>
      <link>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/red-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:34:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/red-screen/</guid>
      <description>Discover Blackscreen.space, where the vibrant and captivating essence of red comes to life. We recognize red as a compelling color, rich with meanings and associations. Blackscreen.space offers a dynamic platform centered on red screens, igniting powerful emotions, boosting energy, and enhancing visuals to enrich your digital experience. The Psychological Impact of Red Screen Bold and Powerful Stimulus Red has long been celebrated as an attention-grabbing hue, serving as a potent visual trigger. Its psychological resonance spans a wide spectrum—symbolizing strength and nobility in some cultures, while evoking anger, passion, or joy in others. This versatility makes red a dynamic tool for stirring emotions and conveying cultural significance. Igniting Passion and Energy Known for sparking passion and vitality, red stirs feelings of</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Screen</title>
      <link>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/green-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:07:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/green-screen/</guid>
      <description>Step into Blackscreen.space and experience the ultimate allure of green.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Screen</title>
      <link>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/blue-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:48:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/blue-screen/</guid>
      <description>Step into Blackscreen.space and experience the ultimate allure of blue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Screen</title>
      <link>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/whitescreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 11:31:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/whitescreen/</guid>
      <description>Discover Blackscreen.space, where pure, radiant white takes center stage. We believe simplicity and clarity are the foundation of an exceptional visual experience. The Power of White Screen Pure and Crisp Visuals Blackscreen.space delivers the stunning beauty of a white screen. Like a pristine digital canvas, it makes your images and photos stand out with remarkable clarity. Whether you’re duplicating visuals or starting a fresh design, a white screen is the perfect backdrop for precision and creativity, enhancing your visual output. Optimized Lighting and Balance With Blackscreen.space, achieving ideal lighting is effortless. From portrait photography to professional studio setups, the white screen serves as a dependable light source, ensuring even and soft illumination. Its bright white tone adds brilliance and depth to your creative projects, helping you craft outstanding visual compositions. Practical Benefits of White Screen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Screen</title>
      <link>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/blackscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 10:04:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/posts/blackscreen/</guid>
      <description>Step into Blackscreen.space and experience the ultimate allure of a black screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 10:54:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crazykids.tech/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Memora: Read It Later App for iOS &amp;amp; macOS with Offline Reading: Memora is a secure read it later app for iOS and macOS. Save web pages offline, sync via iCloud, and enjoy distraction-free reading. Organize with tags and search easily. Black Screen: Your ultimate destination for harnessing the allure of black. xvm: [node|golang|python] Version Manager xvm-windows: [node|golang|python] Version Manager It is friday?: Check if it is friday? The best day of the week. Unix TimeStamp Converter Online: how to convert datetime to timestamp, online timestamp converter, Unix timestamp to datetime, free timestamp converter, timestamp generator Contact me E-mail: duanhjlt{at}gmail.com Github: duan0120 X: @duanhjlt Telegram: @duanhjlt</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
